but look, you say Crimea is yours, you
а вот смотри ты говоришь Крым ваш ты в
are studying to become a
Челябинской области учишься на
tractor driver in the Chelyabinsk region, you say Crimea is yours, and you
тракториста говоришь Крым ваш А ты в
were
Крыму была
once in Crimea, that you were once in Crimea,
когда-то что ты в Крыму когда-то была
no, where have you
нет А где ты вообще была В каких
been? In which countries in any countries have you not been Where?
странах в странах ни в каких не была Где
you've been to the sea
ты на море
anywhere from the cities You're
нигде из городах Вы
from Chelyabinsk region I understand I know the
откуда Челябинская область понял Знаю
Chelyabinsk region is the
Челябинская область это
Urals Yes, how
Урал Да сколько вам
old are you 20 I understand I'm 43 I'm a Psychologist And
лет 20 Понял я Мне 43 я Психолог А вы на
who are you studying for or
кого учитесь или кем
working for I'm studying to be a tractor driver
работаете Я на тракториста учусь
seriously a girl tractor driver unexpectedly
серьёзно девушка тракторист неожиданно
yes
да
yes Where is the carburetor on the tractor  there is
да Где у трактора карбюратор находится
no
нету
tractor, I understand Maybe you are not tractors,
трактора понял Может вы не трактори
deceive me, you
обманывайте меня
are deceiving me, there is What
обманываете есть На каком вы
course are you in at the First And what, how did you
курсе на Первом А что как это вы в 20
go to
лет пошли
study at the age of 20? I just studied before to be a
учиться Я просто училась до этого на
cook, I understand And your girlfriend is
повара понял А подружка ваша на кого
studying to be a student in the fourth grade Oh, she is moving on to the fifth,
учится в четвёртом классе Ой в пятой
I understand  Don’t need it then don’t
переходит понял Не надо её тогда не надо
look, what are you communicating here,
смотрите а чём вы тут общаетесь
what are you communicating here, tractor driver
что а чём общаетесь тут трактористка
future How much is a
будущее Сколько в России зарплата
tractor driver’s salary in Russia Well, it depends where Well, here in the
тракториста Ну смотря где Ну вот у вас в
Chelyabinsk
Челябинской
region, probably well, from petit de to 100 is
области наверно ну от пти де до 100
probably not bad, 500 dollars and a maximum of
наверное неплохо 500 долларов и максимум
1,000 is also good  Yeah, what did they decide to be a
1.000 тоже хорошо Угу А что решили они
cook and a tractor driver?
поваром а тракторист кой
Yes, I just
быть Да мне просто надо
needed my mom to receive money from the state. So
было чтобы мама деньги от государства
what’s the joke and Mom
получала Так в чём прикол а Мама
gets money from the state. If you
получает деньги от государства Если вы
study somewhere, yes. What’s the joke? Once again
учитесь да А в чём прикол ещё раз у
she gets it; I’m an adult  Well,
неё получается я это совершеннолетняя же
well, we have two more small
вот а у нас ещё двое маленьких
children and it turns out that while I’m not studying, I’m not
детей и получается пока я не учусь я не
considered a
считаюсь
child, I don’t understand again, three bli until
ребёнком не понял ещё раз трем бли пока
you can’t, on the contrary, while you’re studying, you
вы не может наоборот пока вы учитесь то
consider him a child Yes, while I’m studying, I’m
считаете ребёнком Да пока я учусь Я
considered a child, and that is, you’re your mother
считаюсь ребёнком а то есть вас вас мама
sent after after what grade did you
отправила после после какого класса вы
go to become a cook after what after the
пошли на повара после дего после
ninth grade did you go how long? Well, you
девятого класса вы пошли сколько Вот вот
studied to be a
учились на
cook for 4 years, I graduated, that is, Yeah,
повара 4 года я закончила то есть Ага вы
after the ninth grade you went to the ninth
после девятого класса пошли в девятом
grade How old were you 15 15 a 4
классе Вам сколько лет было 15 15 а 4
years before children  We studied so that you did
года до дети учились для того чтобы Вы
n’t want to be a cook, but you studied so
не хотели на повара но учились для того
that your mother would receive an allowance for you, so
чтобы мама получала пособие на вас так
yes, yes, and now we went to become a tractor driver, too, so that our
да да и сейчас пошли на тракторист тоже
mother would receive an allowance. And
чтобы мама получала пособие А на повар
I went to become a cook, Because I wanted to, and to become a
Это я пошла Потому что сама хотела а на
tractor driver. We went because you need to get
тракториста Пошли потому что нужно
paid.  allowance yes Danya And until how many
получать пособие да Даня А до скольки
years do you want to study until the end
лет вы так хотите учиться до ца до
of the day Well, I’ll finish studying and that’s it and
сока Ну вот закончу учиться и всё и
go to work And how long does it take to study to become a tractor driver for
пойду работать А сколько на тракториста
2 years 2 years I understand that is, after
учится 2 года 2 года понял то есть через
2 years my mother will no longer receive
2 года мама уже не будет получать
an allowance yes Well,
пособие да Ну
yes, an interesting scheme  And dad What does
да интересная схема А папа Чем
he do according to the facts?
занимается по фактам
It works in the north
работает это на севере
Yes no And where in any x in Perm I seem to
Да нет А где в любых х в Перми вроде
understand, well, some settings
понял ну настройки какие-то
Yes
Да
I understand It’s interesting, but it turns out that the younger ones,
понял Интересно а получается младшие
when they grow up, will also go to study so that
когда вырастут тоже пойдут учиться чтобы
mom gets paid And mom, who does
мама получала оплату А мама кем
mom work? She doesn’t work in  on maternity leave
работает мама Не работает она в декрете
and the smallest one is
а самая маленькая сколько
2 years old and we are 2 years old. So you burn for
2 года и мы бом 2 года Так ты же гори
someone there,
кому-то там
four is not next to you, I studied for a year
четыре нет рядом с тобой я года училась
to be a cook, well, she’s sitting next to you. How
на повара ну рядом с тобой сидит Сколько
old is the
лет
person next to her? 10 years old. This is a
человек рядом 10 лет Это двоюродная
cousin. And I understood everything. And at my mother’s.  twins Yes,
сестра А всё понял А у мамы двойня Да
two-year-old twins Yes,
двойня двухлетних Да всё
I understood everything And how much allowance they give to your mother,
понял А сколько пособие дают на вас маме
I
я не
wasn’t interested in it, I understood And you already have a
интересовалась понял А у тебя есть
boyfriend,
парень
well, you don’t want to get married so that you have
уже был ну ты не хочешь замуж чтоб тоже
children too No, I don’t want children yet. Moreover,
детей Нет пока не хочу детей так Тем
I understand because yes, that’s
понял потому что это же да Это
so much  It’s true that money is spent on them and
столько денег на них уходит правда и
they will have to be sent to study to become a
придётся их отправлять учиться на
tractor driver. And it’s not that money is spent,
тракториста Да и не то что денег уходит
I just look at my little
я вот просто смотрю на свою маленькую
sister and I don’t have any desire to
сестру и у меня всё Желание отпадает
give birth. I understand. Whose Crimea do you
рожать понял А чей Крым Как ты
think what do you think whose
считаешь что как ты считаешь чей
cream is ours? I understand Yes  how often do you look
крем наш понял Да как ты часто смотришь
at your
на свою сестру
little sister that how often do you look at
маленькую что как ты часто смотришь на
your
свою сестру
little sister the sound was interrupted I didn’t understand how
маленькую звук прервался Я не поняла как
often you look at your little
часто ты смотришь на свою маленькую
sister
сестру
every day I understood Look more often look
каждый день понял Смотри чаще смотри
several times a
несколько раз в
day
день
why is this such a
почему это такая
joke look more
шутка больше смотри
at But look  you say Crimea is
на А вот смотри ты говоришь Крым
yours you are in the Chelyabinsk region studying to be a
ваш ты в Челябинской области учишься на
tractor driver you say Yeah And you
тракториста говоришь Ага А ты в Крыму
were
была
once in Crimea that you were once in Crimea
когда-то что ты в Крыму когда-то была
no Where have you been in any
нет А где ты вообще была В каких
countries in any countries Where have
странах в странах ни в каких не была Где
you been at sea
ты на море
nowhere so I understand correctly
нигде так я правильно понимаю
you live in the Chelyabinsk region somewhere in
ты живёшь в Челябинской области где-то в
some town or village village or
каком-то посёлке или селе село или
town village yes you live in the
посёлок посёлок да ты живёшь в
Chelyabinsk region in the
Челябинской области в
village you will be
посёлке будешь
a tractor driver never in your life been to the
тракторист никогда в жизни не была ни в
Crimea or anywhere at sea Not
Крыму ни вообще где-то на море Не говоря
speaking of other countries, but you say that
уже о других странах но ты говоришь что
Crimea is yours. Why do you need
Крым ваш Зачем тебе
Crimea, I don’t know, not to me, to Putin, well, to Putin, and
Крым не знаю не мне Путину Ну Путину А
so say that Crimea is Putin. You say that
так скажи что Крым Путин Ты же говориш
Crimea is ours. Like yours,
Крым наш Типа твой
it turns out.
получается
No, you’re happy that Putin took
Нет ты довольна от того что Путин забрал
Crimea and
Крым и
Ukraine, that Putin you you  I’m happy that
Украины что Путин ты ты довольна что
Putin took Crimea from
Путин забрал Крым у
Ukraine, the sound was interrupted, you’re happy that
Украины звук прерывался ты довольна что
Ukraine Yes, it’s somehow neutral
Украины Да как-то нейтрально
neutral That is, it turns out that
нейтрально То есть получается
when Crimea returns to Ukraine, you
когда Крым вернётся в Украину ты не
won’t be
будешь
against it Well, yes, I understand, but I do
против Ну да понял а Донецк Луганск
n’t know whose Donetsk Lugansk ours is good Why did Putin
чей не знаю наш хорошо А зачем Путин
attack  to Ukraine and took Crimea Donetsk
напал на Украину и забрал Крым Донецк
Lugansk not
Луганск не
[music]
[музыка]
I don’t know what you think because Putin
знаю как ты считаешь изза того что Путин
started the war, is it better for you to live in the
начал войну вам лучше стало жить в
Chelyabinsk region or worse why
Челябинской области или хуже почему
Putin started the war Putin started the war or
Путин начал войну Путин начал войну или
not Zelensky seems to have started the war how
нет Зеленский вроде начал войну как
Zelensky started the war attacked Russia
Зеленский начал войну напал на Россию
Tell me I don’t know if you don’t
Расскажи мне я не знаю так если не
know Why do you open your mouth and
знаешь Зачем ты открываешь рот и
say it started the war you were
говоришь это начал войну ты у
bombed for 8 years some city
де бомбили 8 лет город какой-то
joined that was bombed for 8 years a
присоединился который бомбили 8 лет
ten year old child yes yes she
десятилетний ребёнок да да она больше
knows more I have
знает у меня к
a wish for you look at your little sister more often
тебе пожелание смотри чаще на маленькую
It’s good that you do
сестричку хорошо чтоб ты
n’t Okay,
не Ладно
thank you, I’ll take it into account Yeah,
спасибо я учту
yeah
Угу угу
Listen, why did
Слушай а почему у
you
тебя
go No, really, Well, why Well, because I’m licking
пошёл Не ну реально Ну почему Ну потому
what you’re licking You’re licking
что лижу что ты лижешь Ты лижешь
Damn, don’t lie so much, you’re
Блин да не лежи столько много ты
climbing over your cheeks already in short, yes
перелезая щёки уже короче да
Damn, in short, it’s all nonsense in general
Блин короче всё бред вообще
Give a new one  channel pidpishit on nyogo
Дава це новый канал пидпишить на нього
directly immediately Put the dialer to remove the
прямо зараз Постав дзвоник чтоб отримати
SPO vchennya we will be
ус СПО вчення будем на
connected to L
звязку L